<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>John CS</title>
        <link>http://johncs.com</link>
        <description>Blog of John Christopher Sullivan</description>
        <item>
            <title>The Seesaw - A D&amp;D 5E Encounter</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/dnd-seesaw-room.htm</link>
            <description>
I've been DMing a Dungeons and Dragons (fifth edition) game every other week for awhile. During this last session on Monday they found themselves in the center of a room with a rectangular floor.

</description>
            <pubDate>April 19, 2017</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A very practical piece of pure CS</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/loop-termination.htm</link>
            <description>
If an interviewer asked me to find the last item in a linked list, I might write some code like this:

</description>
            <pubDate>March 8, 2017</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Could I be a zealot? Yes and it sucks.</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/zealotry.htm</link>
            <description>
Zealotry seems to always sneak up on me. I see it in my coworkers, myself, and of course in comments online. Recognizing it in myself is challenging, but I'm slowly building up some tools to help me out. This post is about one such tool.

</description>
            <pubDate>March 4, 2017</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A model of (polyamorous) relationships</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/polyamory-model.htm</link>
            <description>
I want to present a model for thinking about relationships and polyamory. Like any model, I will relate it (hopefully strongly) to real world things, but the model exists within its own system.

</description>
            <pubDate>January 18, 2017</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Principles of Building a Simple Site</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/building-websites.htm</link>
            <description>
I've made a bunch of simple websites over the years, and from my endless failures I've built up some principles I now follow.

</description>
            <pubDate>July 30, 2016</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>I talk to myself on GitHub</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/monologues.htm</link>
            <description>
<a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/brownhead/phial/issues/1">I</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/brownhead/mangoengine/issues/7">talk</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/brownhead/superzippy/issues/11">to</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/brownhead/mangoengine/issues/2">myself</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/galah-group/galah/issues/399">on</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/acm-ucr/hub/issues/8">GitHub</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/galah-group/galah/issues/393">a</a> <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/Khan/engblog/issues/21">lot</a>. If I could share our internal issues at <a class="reference external" href="https://www.khanacademy.org">Khan Academy</a> you'd see a similar story there as well. I do this to serve a few ends.

</description>
            <pubDate>June 10, 2015</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Solving a wooden puzzle</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/damn-puzzle.htm</link>
            <description>
Last week a mysterious double-sided puzzle appeared next to the kitchen at <a class="reference external" href="https://www.khanacademy.org/">Khan Academy</a>.

</description>
            <pubDate>April 27, 2015</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Typos in search queries at Khan Academy</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/spellchecker.htm</link>
            <description>
One year ago, searching for <em>polinomials</em> on <a class="reference external" href="https://www.khanacademy.org/search">Khan Academy's search page</a> would give you no results. If you typed the same thing into Google you'd be efficiently and politely corrected.

</description>
            <pubDate>April 11, 2015</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Local Storage Today</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/6-localstorage.htm</link>
            <description>
I'd like to write to <tt class="docutils literal">localStorage</tt> often. I'd also like to write to it synchronously in response to user interaction. Past wisdom says this is a bad idea and will give me Angry Users Syndrome very quickly.

</description>
            <pubDate>December 22, 2014</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Intelligently Shortening Text</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/5-highlighting.htm</link>
            <description>
Our search page at Khan Academy displays highlighting information to provide context for our results. Our full-text search engine gives us the highlighting text, but it doesn't provide a way to reliably control the length of the text. The end result can be undesirable.

</description>
            <pubDate>May 18, 2014</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Python Import System</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/4-python-import.htm</link>
            <description>
I made a presentation at Khan Academy on a few good things to know about Python's import system. Here's a writeup of that presentation (this is written mostly as a reference, sorry for the dryness).

</description>
            <pubDate>March 31, 2014</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Transactions with Python's sqlite3 Package</title>
            <link>http://johncs.com/posts/1-sqlite3_transactions.htm</link>
            <description>
Python's <tt class="docutils literal">sqlite3</tt> package tries to take care of the tricky business of properly executing <tt class="docutils literal">BEGIN</tt> and <tt class="docutils literal">COMMIT</tt> statements. The rules of when and how this automatic transactioning is done has confounded a number of developers, many of whom have jumped ship and chosen to use the <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/rogerbinns/apsw">aspw</a> package or similar.

</description>
            <pubDate>March 5, 2014</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
